{
  "category1": {
    "links": [
      "https://example1.com",
      "https://example2.com",
      "https://example3.com"
    ]
  },
  "category2": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 1 de categoría 2?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 2 de categoría 2?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 3
      }
    ]
  },
  "category3": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 1 de categoría 3?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 2 de categoría 3?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 2
      }
    ]
  },
  "category4": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 1 de categoría 4?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 2 de categoría 4?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 1
      }
    ]
  },
  "category5": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 1 de categoría 5?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 2 de categoría 5?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 0
      }
    ]
  },
  "category6": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 1 de categoría 6?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "¿Pregunta 2 de categoría 6?",
        "options": ["Opción 1", "Opción 2", "Opción 3", "Opción 4"],
        "answerIndex": 2
      }
    ]
  }
}
